A Guide to the Virginia Miscellany Papers, 1657-1931
Library of Virginia
- Legal papers, 1657-1862 (Box 1-2)
  - Legal Papers, 1787-1789 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Allotment, 11 February 1789, Joseph Prentis and Cuthbert Bullitt allotted judges of the District Court at Winchester and Monongalia [County] for the next term. Signed by J. Mercer, Richard Parker, Edmund Winston, Richard Cary, James Henry, and John Tyler., 2 p.
    - Execution, 18 February 1789, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Ca. resp. requiring George Eskridge to answer Thomas Garnett., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 24 February 1789, from Richard Ransome of Berkeley [County] to George Hite., 2 p.
    - Bond, 15 April 1789, Meshach Sexton and Samuel Dooley of Frederick County to Isaac Hite, Jr., executor of Cary MacDonald, deceased., 1 leaf, copy.
  - Legal Papers, 1789-1791 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Promissory note, 20 April 1789, from George Braxton to Joseph Tidball., 1 leaf.
    - Deposition, 12 May 1789, testimony of Job Eldridge in the action of Bryant Sloan v. George Rust. Nelson County, [Virginia]., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 1 July 1789, James Jones of Lancaster County to John Jones of Richmond County., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Deposition, 3 September 1789, testimony of Michael Thorn concering flour of Anthony Wrightenhour [Rittenhaur?]. Alexandria., 2 p.
    - Bond, 17 October 1789, Warner Washington and Albion Throckmorton to Messrs. Hubert and Poote., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 16 January 1790, William Throckmorton and Warner Washington to James McCrea., 4 p., copy.
    - Bond, 29 April 1790, Warner Washington, Jr., and Albion Throckmorton to Horatio Gates and Mary, his wife, administrators of Bartholomew Booth, deceased., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 26 June 1790, Isaac Zane, iron master, to Frederick Conrad of Winchester., 2 p.
    - Bond, 9 July 1790, John Cook and Colonel William Darke to Robert Throckmorton, sheriff of Berkeley County., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Deed, 6 April 1791, for tract of land in Frederick County from Lancelott Lee of Berkeley County to Roger Barton of Berkeley County. Recorded in Frederick County 6 April 1791., 2 p., incomplete.
  - Legal Papers, 1791-1792 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Execution, 18 April 1791, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Ca. resp. requiring Albion Throckmorton to answer George M. Deadrick, assignee of Benjamin Berry, Jr., 2 p.
    - Bond, 18 June 1791, Albion Throckmorton and Warner Washington to William Armstrong., 2 p., copy.
    - Receipt, 9 June 1791, Beal Fowler to James Hickley., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 9 September 1791, from James Rose to Miller Hoze., 2 p.
    - Deed, 3 September 1791, for lots number 65 and 44 in the town of Winchester from James Mercer of Fredericksburg, Spotsylvania County, to John Duffield of Frederick County. Recorded in Winchester 3 September 1791., 2 p.
    - Suit, 10 September 1791, Michael McKewn and James O'Hara v. John Cooke, consisting of commission, 10 September 1791, to Hilary Baker and John Baker, aldermen of Philadelphia, for the examination of Joseph Nourse, witness for the plaintiffs; and interrogatories and deposition, 5 January 1792, of Joseph Nourse., 6 p.
    - Receipt, 6 October 1791, John Conrad to W. J. Kercheval., 2 p.
    - Allotment, 21 November 1791, Joseph Prentis and Joseph Jones allotted judges of the District Court at Winchester and Monongalia [County] for the next term, signed by Joseph Prentis, John Tyler, James Henry, Joseph Jones, Spencer Roane, and William Nelson, Jr., 1 leaf.
    - Declaration, March 1792, Patrick and William Bogles and Colin Dunlop complaining of Henry Hardin. Frederick County., 2 p.
    - Bond, 27 March 1792, Cornelius Ferree, Thomas Collins, Okey Johnson, Perez Drew, and John Higgins to Abraham Johnson, Ignatius Wheeler, John Mitchell, William Fox, and Isaac Parsons. Recorded Hampshire County 27 March 1792., 2 p., copy.
  - Legal Papers, 1792-1794 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Execution, 19 July 1792, to unknown. Fi. Fa. to levy goods of John Cook. Neil Buchanan and Duncan Rose, executors of John Banister, v. John Cook., 2 p.
    - Court order, October 1792, from Frederick County Court concerning a road from Battletown to Stubblefield town mill., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Account, 1790-1793, Doctor John Nelson, Alexandria, to William Hodgson, administrator of estate of W. Stribling, deceased., 4 p.
    - Account, 1785-1793, John Smith and Edward Smith to W. L. Lee, executor of Thomas Smith., 1 leaf.
    - Account, January-May 1793, Warner Washington to Hodgson Nicholson., 2 p.
    - Deposition, 7 June 1793, testimony of Patrick Woodrow in the action of James Tapscott v. Robert Throckmorton. Frederick County. Enclosure: letter, 18 September 1786, from Robert Throckmorton, Virginia, to Robert Cary, merchant, London., 3 p.
    - Bond, 31 August 1793, Thomas Throckmorton and William Throckmorton of Frederick County to John Koontz., 2 p., copy.
    - Promissory note, 6 December 1793, from Warner Washington to S. Smith and Buchanan., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Chancery suit papers, 1779-1794, in Frederick County Court, Weedon v. Hampton. Containing 1) Plea, 9 August 1788, of Nathaniel Weedon and Mary his wife, administrators of John Smith, deceased, of Fauquier County for injunction against Richard and Wade Hampton; 2) copy of plea; 3)Answer, 7 December 1791, of Richard and Wade Hampton; 4) Bond, 17 October 1788, Nathaniel Weedon, Minor Winn, and Charles West to Henry Hampton; 5) Receipt, 4 August 1781, Wade Hampton to Mrs. Mary Smith; 6) receipt, 10 March [1781?], Richard and Wade Hampton to Captain John Smith; 7) Promissory note, 28 April 1782, Mary Smith to Richard and Wade Hampton; 8) Receipt, 28 April 1782, R. Hampton to Mrs. Mary Smith; 9) Account, 1779-1786, Mrs. Mary Smith, now Weedon, to Richard Hampton; 10) bill of sale, 18 November 1779, for five slaves from Richard and Wade Hampton of South Carolina to John Smith; 11) Answer, 10 December 1794, of Henry Hampton., 17 p. and 7 leaves.
    - Account, 5 August 1794, William Groverman to Hodgson Nicholson., 1 leaf.
  - Legal Papers, 1794-1795 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Protest, 19 August 1794, Southgate and Consett of London, merchants, to Thomas Daniel and Company, concerning bill of exchange from D. Morton to Thomas Daniel and Company, merchants, London, regarding Miller Southgate., 4 p.
    - Bond, 8 October 1794, Isaac Zane and John Peyton to David Kennedy, sheriff of Frederick County., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 8 October 1794, Isaac Zane and John Peyton to David Kennedy, High Sheriff of Frederick County., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Account, February-March 1795, Adam Hickman to Richard Holliday., 2 p.
    - Certificate of discharge, 13 June 1795, Gabriel Hayes of Colonel Moses Rawlings' regiment, for service in the Revolution. Signed Robert Denny, auditor., 1 leaf.
    - Promissory note, 26 June 1795, from William Johnston to Peacock and Wrenshall. Dated Philadelphia., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 7 August 1795, from Richard Holliday to George Roberts and Josiah Twamley. Dated Winchester., 2 p.
    - Advertisement, [2 September 1795], concerning the sale of estate of Isaac Zane. Zane's will was probated at Winchester 2 September 1795. This undated advertisement may date from about 1800., 2 p.
    - Account, 2 November 1795, Mrs. Milly Throckmorton to James Russell., 2 p.
    - Account, 1793-1795, Messrs. William Wilson and Company of Alexandria in account with the estate of Andrew Clow., 7 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1795-1797 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Bond, 9 November 1795, John Williams and Francis Postgate, both of Frederick County, to Joshua Swayne of Frederick County., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 6 February 1796, Charles M. Thurston of Frederick County and Joseph Tidbal to Hugh Holmes., 2 p., copy.
    - Power of attorney, 30 April 1796, Catherine Douglas, Sr., Archibald Douglas, and Catherine Douglas, Jr., of Scotland, to Alexander Henderson of Dumfries, Prince William County. Recorded in Frederick County 30 April 1798., 4 p.
    - Account, 23 July 1796, Aaron Kee to William Wood., 2 p.
    - Account, 10 September 1796, Abraham Lindo to Robert Bridges., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 26 November 1796, George Eskridge, Thomas Pilkington, and John Randolph, to Robert Chinn., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Bond, 29 November 1796, John Randolph and Thomas Pilkington to Elisha Johnston., 2 p. copy.
    - Promissory note, 17 December 1796, from Holliday and McDonald to Joseph Cary., 2 p.
    - Bond, 20 December 1796, John Bayles Armistead of Prince William Counnty for self and Daniel Morgan of Frederick County to Thomas Douglass., 2 p.
    - Bond, 2 January 1797, Gabriel Nourse of Charlestown, Berkeley County, to George Stubblefield., 2 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1797 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Bond, 4 January 1797, John Lindsay of Frederick County to Hanna Washington, executor of Colonel Warner Washington, deceased., 2 p., copy.
    - Promissory note, 19 January 1797, from Joseph Hale, Jr., and Thomas Lindsay, both of Frederick County, to Emilia Throckmorton., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 24 June 1797, Robert Cockburn, Amos Nichols, William Riddles, and David Hunter to Smith Slaughter, George Matthews, Benjamin Foreman, Gabriel Hays, and William Darke., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Receipt, 25 June 1797, R. [unknown] to Captain Thomas Lewis., 2 p.
    - Deed, 12 May 1797, for 383 acres in Frederick County from Francis Craycroft and Elizabeth, his wife, of Alexandria, Fairfax County, to John Darby of Alexandria, Fairfax County. Recorded in Fairfax County 18 July 1797., 4 p.
    - Account, May-August 1797, Joseph H. Jones to Levi Taylor., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 15 August 1797, John Holker and Rawleigh [Raleigh] Colston to George Stubblefield., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Account, June-September 1797, Charles Folk in account with John and David McKaleb., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 4 September 1797, from William Johnston to William A. Hipkins., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Promissory note, 9 September 1797, William [Moseley?] to Henry Zimmerman., 2 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1797-1798 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Promissory note, 14 September 1797, from Moses Cox of Berkeley County to Winn Winship., 2 p.
    - Execution, 6 October 1797, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Ca. resp. requiring John Rust to answer Benjamin Rust., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 13 October 1797, from George Allen and Abraham Traft to Mrs. Hannah Washington., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Bond, 26 October 1797, David Hunter and Philip Pendleton of Martinsburg, Berkeley County, to William Taylor of Baltimore, Maryland., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 4 November 1797, Lawrence A. Washington and Van Rutherford to James Wood., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Bond, 30 November 1797, Robert Mercer, Lewis Banett, and Thomas Babb to James Wood., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Deed, 5 May 1795, for 300 acres in Frederick County from George Braxton and Mary, his wife, of King William County to Benjamin Harrison of Brandon, Prince George County. Recorded in Frederick County 4 December 1797., 4 p.
    - Bond, 2 February 1798, Alexander Pitt Buckman of Berkeley County to Edward Gante of Berkeley County., 2 p., copy.
    - Promissory note, 14 February 1798, from Charles M. Thurston to Adam Douglass., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 5 May 1798, William Groverman, Robert Young,and John Foster of Alexandria to George Repold., 1 leaf, copy.
  - Legal Papers, 1798-1799 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Bond, 5 May 1798, Tarlton F. Webb of Frederick County to William Hodgson of Alexandria., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Account, 15 May 1798, Charles G. Pelaskie to an unknown individual., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 20 May 1798, George Brittain of Prince William County to Richard Vertch, James Wilson, and William J. Hall of Alexandria, trustees of Washington J. Washington and Company., 2 p.
    - Bond, 20 May 1798, George Brittain of Prince William County to Richard Vertch, James Wilson, and William J. Hall of Alexandria, trustees of Washington J. Washington and Company., 2 p.
    - Notice, 18 June 1798, George Repold to William Groverman, Robert Young, and John Foster, regarding bond., 2 p.
    - Execution, 20 September 1798, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Ca. resp. requiring Warner Washington to answer Robert Burwell, assignee of Harfield Timberlake., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 8 October 1798, from Bemjamin Rooch to Druscilla Ball., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Execution, 20 December 1798, to the sheriff of Fairfax County. Ca. resp. requiring William Hodgson, administrator of William Stribling, deceased, to answer James Usher, executor of Abraham Usher, deceased., 2 p.
    - Petition, 1799, Bushrod Taylor, assignee of Daniel Morgan, v. Isaac Henry. Frederick County., 1 leaf.
    - Account, 22 January-5 April 1799, John Kingan to Richard Baillie., 1 leaf.
  - Legal Papers, 1799-1800 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Summons, 13 July 1799, to the sheriff of Frederick County commanding him to summon Isaac Hendry [Henry] to answer the petition of Bushrod Taylor, assignee of Daniel Morgan., 2 p.
    - Receipt, 24 April 1799, James McDonald to John Thurston., 2 p.
    - Execution, 5 October 1799, to the sheriff of Fairfax County. Ca. resp. requiring Henry Lee to answer Joseph Smith., 1 leaf.
    - Account, February 1798-February 1800, John Castleman to Thomas Stephenson., 3 p.
    - Promissory note, 11 March 1800, from C. M. Thurston to General [Daniel] Morgan., 2 p.
    - Suit, 1796-1800, Robert Rogers v. Joshua Gore, consisting of: 1) Account, 1796-1798, Joshua Gore to Robert Rogers; 2) execution, 29 March 1800, to the sheriff of Frederick County, Ca. resp.; 3) declaration, n.d., of Robert Rogers., 6 p. and 1 leaf.
    - Writ of habeas corpus, 8 April 1800, to George Steptoe Washington, captain in the 8th United States Regiment, commanding him to bring William Carothers before Judge Robert White, Jr., 3 p.
    - Narratio, 28 April 1800, Edward Howe v. Joseph Pangle and Henry Pangle., 1 leaf.
    - Account, December 1794-August 1800, Thomas and Samuel Nowell of Winchester in account with Prager and Company., 4 p.
    - Deed, 10 September 1800, for 478 acres in Frederick County from Jaems McDonald and Mary, his wife, of Frederick County to William Heth of Henrico County, [Virginia]., 6 p., copy.
  - Legal Papers, 1800-1802 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Bond, 22 October 1800, Samuel Crumpton and John Marshall to Elisha Williams, High Sheriff of Frederick County., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Deed, 3 August 1800, for lot number 7 in Winchester from John Kingan of Winchester and Frances, his wife, formerly Frances Walker, daughter of James Walker, deceased, of Winchester to Denton Jacques of Washington County, Maryland. Recorded in Winchester 3 January 1801., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 9 January 1801, Simon Morgan to Landon Carter., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Bond, 22 May 1801, LeRoy Daingerfield to James McDonald., 2 p., copy.
    - Statement, 27 September 1801, George S. Washington to Clerk of Frederick District Court regarding the confession of judgment in suit of Thomas McCormack, assignee of Isaac Larue, et. al. v. George S. Washington., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 5 March 1802, Charles M. Thurston to Newley and Chuun., 2 p., copy.
    - Promissory note, 28 September 1802, from John Smith to Harry Heth., 1 leaf.
    - Indictment, 1 November 1802, Frederick County Court, Commonwealth v. Thomas Buckhannon [Buchanan]. Buckhannon charged with assaulting Israel Janney., 1 leaf.
    - Summons, 8 November 1802, to the sheriff of Frederick County commanding him to summon Thomas Buchanan to answer his indictment., 1 leaf.
    - Execution, 3 December 1802, to the sheriff of Frederick County. Ca. resp. requiring Joseph Pangle and Henry Pangle to answer Edward Howe., 2 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1802-1803 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Bond, 24 December 1802, Joseph Pangle, Henry Pangle, and Samuel Baker to Thomas Massie, High Sheriff of Frederick County., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Suit, 1803, John Howsman v. Presley Talbott containing: 1) Narratio and bill, n.d; and 2) Execution, 3 February 1803, Ca. resp., 3 p.
    - Bond, 5 February 1803, David Hunter of Martinsburg to Alexander and James Fulton of Baltimore, Maryland., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Receipt, 22 February 1803, William Anderson and Thomas Buchannan [Buchanan] to Thomas Shepard., 2 p.
    - Plea, 20 April 1803, Edward Williams, otherwise Doctor Williams, assignee of John Thurston, complaining of James McDowell. Frederick County., 2 p.
    - Promissory note, 29 April 1803, from John Smith to Joseph Tidball., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 28 July 1803, Warner Washington to Presly Neville, executor of Daniel Morgan, deceased., 2 p., copy.
    - Bond, 20 August 1803, Warner Washington and Mordecai Throckmorton to Presly Neville, executor of Daniel Morgan, deceased., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Promissory note, 20 September 1803, Samuel Kercheval to Presly Talbott., 2 p., copy.
    - Order, 4 November 1803, Amos Allison to Stephen K. Stephens and Company, merchants, New York, concerning Messrs. Hawthorne and Taylor., 2 p.
  - Legal Papers, 1803-1804 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Bond, 15 November 1803, John Carter of Frederick County to Charles Lee of Alexandria., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 19 January 1804, William Gregsby and Jacob Weekly to Daniel Henry., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Promissory note, 1 February 1804, from William Snickers to General Presley Neville., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Promissory note, 2 February 1804, from Sarah Churchill to John Sowers., 2 p., copy.
    - Promissory note, 12 March 1804, from Samuel Kercheval to Presley Talbott., 2 p., copy.
    - Release of errors, 22 March 1804, Robert Baylor to John Baylor., 1 leaf.
    - Promissory note, 26 April 1804, Mordecai Booth and Mordecai Throckmorton to Henry Huntsbury., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Commission, 30 May 1804, to Strother G. Settle as Coroner of Frederick County, signed by John Page., 1 leaf.
    - Receipt, 3 December 1804, John C. Wormeley to Thomas Shepherd., 1 leaf.
    - Receipt, 28 December 1804, John C. Wormeley to Thomas Shepherd., 1 leaf.
  - Legal Papers, 1805-1807 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Promissory note, 11 January 1805, from John Cruger Wormeley adn John Wormeley to Rober Baylor., 2 p., copy.
    - Receipt, 21 January 1805, John C. Wormeley to Thomas Shepherd., 1 leaf.
    - Receipt, 26 February 1805, John C. Wormeley to Thomas Shepherd., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 2 August 1805, John C. Wormeley and John Wormeley to John and William Thompson., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Receipt, 3 September 1805, John C. Wormeley to Thomas Shepherd., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 14 November 1805, Patrick Denver and Richard Carr, both of Frederick County, to Nathaniel Cartmell., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Agreement, 30 November 1805, [Henry?] Heth to Joseph Tidball., 2 p., copy.
    - Promissory note, 3 December 1805, from John C. Wormeley to Mrs. Rachael Walker., 2 p.
    - Commission, 20 September 1806, to John B. Tilden as Coroner of Frederick County, signed by William H. Cabell., 1 leaf.
    - Promissory note, 8 April 1807, from Mary Wormeley and John Wormeley to Samuel Irwin., 1 leaf, copy.
  - Legal Papers, 1807-1809 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Bond, 25 May 1807, Patrick Denver, Richard Carr, and Daniel Denver to Isaac Hite, High Sheriff of Frederick County., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Bond, 29 June 1807, William Snickers and John Washington to David Castleman, Jr., 1 leaf, copy.
    - Execution, 5 December 1807, to the marshal of the District of Columbia. Ca. resp. requiring Jonathan and Mahlon Schofield to answer Joseph Smith., 2 p., copy.
    - Deed, 21 May 1808, for 416 acres in Jefferson County from Joshua Swayne and Rebecca, his wife, of Jefferson County to Alex White of Jefferson County., 6 p., copy.
    - Bond, 14 September 1808, John Wormeley, Mary Wormeley, and Thomas Parker to Samuel Irwin., 2 p., copy.
    - Indictment, 1809, Frederick County Court, Commonwealth v. Jeremiah Leonard, Sr., and Jeremiah Leonard, Jr., charged with assaulting Moses Barker., 2 p.
    - Indictment, 1809, Frederick County Court, Commonwealth v. Hezekiah Ponn, charged with assaulting John Latham., 2 p.
    - Indictment, 1809, Frederick County Court, Commonwealth v. James Garner and Samuel Garner, charged with assaulting John Hamilton., 1 leaf.
    - Indictment, 1 leaf.
    - Commission, 20 June 1809, to James Singleton as sheriff of Frederick County, signed by John Tyler., 1 leaf.
  - Legal Papers, 1809-1814 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Bond, 17 February 1809, Mordecai Throckmorton and Fairfax Washington to Micajah Crupper., 4 p.
    - Terms of sale, 24 August 1809, of the land of Mayo Carrington's estate lying on Willis' Creek and Boston Branch, signed E. Carrington and John Adams. With endorsements: 1)E. Carrington, John Adams, Richard Richards; and 2) E. Carrington, John Adams, Benjamin Carrington., 2 p.
    - Certification, 2 March 1810, R. Smith, Secretary for the U.S. Department of State certifies that S. H. Smith and Daniel Rapine are Justices of the Peace for Washington County in the District of Columbia., 1 leaf.
    - Bill, 17 June 1812, Joseph Lewis, Jr., member of Congress from the state of Virginia, to Creed Taylor, Chancellor of the Richmond City District. Plea that writs of subpoena be issued for Peter R. Beverley and Andrew Jamison. concerns sale of land from Beverley to Lewis., 4 p.
    - Summons, 24 June 1812, to the sheriff of Loudoun County, commanding him to summon Peter R. Beverley, Robert Beverley, and Andrew Jamison to answer a bill exhibited against them by Joseph Lewis, Jr., 2 p.
    - Power of attorney, 9 October 1813, Arthur Patterson and Martha his wife, late Martha Allen, William Patterson and Polly his wife, late Polly Allen, Joseph G. William and Elizabeth his wife, late Elizabeth Allen, and Anna Allen, heirs of Robert Allen, deceased, of Frederick County to Robert P. Allen of Shelby County, Kentucky. Recorded in Frederick County 31 January 1814., 5 p.
    - Agreement, 28 July 1813, between Jenings Beckwith and Isaac [unknown]., 1 leaf.
    - Power of attorney, 22 December 1813, Henry W. Calmes of Clarke County, Kentucky, to Thomas Griggs, Sr., of Jefferson County. Recorded in Frederick County 3 August 1814., 4 p.
    - Bond, 2 March 1814, Warner Washington to Presley Neville, executor of Daniel Morgan, deceased., 2 p.
    - Memorandum, 6 July 1814, John McPherson to William J. Craighill, William Little, and Samuel Brown, authorizing payment to Samuel Swayne and money due to Joshua Swayne and Noah Swayne, heirs and legal representatives of Joshua Swayne, deceased., 1 leaf.
  - Legal Papers, 1820-1862 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bill, 18 November 1820, Richard Henry Lee of Loudoun County to Dabney Carr, Judge of the Superior Court of Chancery held at Winchester. Plea for new trial in action of Lee v. Anderson and Smith concerning promissory note of Richard H. Love [Lee?] to Joseph Smith, assignee of James Anderson of Alexandria., 4 p.
    - Notice, 21 September 1821, George Hancock to Warner Washington, Perrin Washington, and Reade Washington regarding bond., 1 leaf.
    - Bond, 9 March 1826, Burr Powell, Humphrey B. Powell, and William L. Powell of Loudoun County to William Sleenbugen and John Morgan of Shenandoah County., 2 p.
    - Register, 6 December 1831, John Hemings as a free man of color., 1 leaf.
    - Receipt, 8 August 1862, Charles B. Dodd, Seminary, Alexandria, to William Forsyth., 1 leaf.
  - Legal Papers, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - scrap, n.d., 2 p.
    - Bill of exchange, 28 February 1762, of Richard Barrett., 2 p.
    - postscript, n.d., to unknown letter., 1 leaf.
    - Account, n.d., of John Briscow., 1 leaf, fragment.
    - cover, n.d., for letter from Henry Lee to Wilson Cary Nicholas., 1 leaf.
    - Fragment, 22 February 1790, of letter from Nathaniel Burwell to Baker Perkins., 1 leaf.
    - List, n.d., of items., 1 leaf.